Hey.
Yeah. Oh... yeah, okay.
Sure.
Look, can we, can we talk
about what happened
here last night?
Sure, just give
me a second
to get all huffy
and weird like you.
Hmm.
Do you believe
that whoever did something
over here last night did
what they did or didn't do?
I mean, come on!
Oh, okay, you really...
you really don't know
what I'm talking about?
No.
Okay.
Last night,
after the party,
I saw Rachel
kissing that jerk from her
office out on your balcony.
Our balcony?
Seriously?
That's so funny
because I told Monica
we should put lights
on our balcony,
and she said "No, no,
it's too cold.
Nobody'll go out there."
And I said, "Maybe
if we put some lights
out there, they will."
Right, that's what I
came over to talk about.
Um, I saw Rachel kissing
some guy on your balcony
even though
there were no lights.
( sighs )
So are you going
talk to her?
What? Why?
Why should I?
I mean, if she wants
to move on, that's fine.
You know when "that's fine"
sounds true?
When someone yells it
and spits.
No, I'm, I'm serious.
I mean, if she wants
to date people, I...
Fine, I don't care,
but she...
at least she could
have told me.
You know, I-I've been
putting my life on hold
and just concentrating
on Emma.
But if she wants
to go out there
kissing guys she barely knows,
well, then, so will I.
Very funny.
Ross is gay.
Ha, ha.
Oh, no, no.
Good.
So you're moving on.
Do you have any idea
where you're moving on to?
I don't know.
I've got plenty
of opportunities.
I mean, just, just now
just now there was
some woman
at the coffeehouse
smiled at me.
And then, uh, the other day
on the subway,
a woman "accidentally"
sat on my hand.
Dude, don't rub my face
in your crazy single life.
Well, and then,
how about this?
There's an anthropologist
at school
who totally came on to me
during the interdepartmental
pot luck dinner.
Why did I get married?!
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ When the rain starts to pour ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Like I've been there before ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey, uh...
let me ask you guys something.
I'm having new headshots
taken tomorrow, right?
And the photographer
said that she thinks
I should have
my eyebrows waxed.
Is that weird for a guy?
Well, it depends.
On?
On how far along he is
in the sex change process.
No, I totally disagree.
No, I think it's fine
for a guy to do
something like that.
Especially an actor.
I mean, not that you need to.
Your eyebrows are...
What?
Okay, stop it, you guys.
Stop staring.
You're freaking me out.
Wow, your knuckles
are kind of hairy, too.
Oh, man, now, I have
to get those done, too?
Wow. Talk about
high maintenance.
Hey, hey, hey.
You dye your hair.
I'm a woman.
Ah, double standards.
Oh, before I forget,
are you coming to
Mike's piano bar tonight?
Only if I don't have
to get up and sing.
But everybody sings.
It's so much fun.
Last time this adorable
old man got up there.
Forgot all the
words, flipped out,
everyone booed him
off the stage.
It was so funny.
I'm just, I'm not
good at singing.
Oh, what's
the matter?
You scared?
Huh? You afraid
I'm a better singer?
You afraid I'm going
to beat you at singing?
Nope, nope. It's
not working on me.
Wow.
I must be
growing up.
Okay, fine.
Just please come
and support Mike.
You don't have to sing.
Okay, so I don't
have to sing,
and I can just sit there
and pass judgment on others?
While drinking.
Ha!
I'm there.
Hi, you guys.
Listen, I really
need your help.
I think I did something
really stupid.
Well, yes, Rachel,
but you got something
so beautiful out of it.
No, not that!
You guys, I kissed Gavin
last night.
Oh, my God!
You kissed him?
Yep. It was after the party.
We were on the balcony, and...
Wait, wait, wait.
I was at home the whole time.
How did I miss that?
Well, it was
the end of the party.
You were probably ironing
wrapping paper.
Oh, yeah.
So how did you end up kissing?
Well, we were all alone, and he
was being really nice to me...
and oh, and he gave me
this scarf.
I thought you hated him.
Well, you know, honey,
there is a thin line
between love and hate,
and, uh, it turns out
that line is a scarf.
So are you thinking
of starting something up
with this guy?
I don't know.
It's so complicated.
I work with this guy,
you know?
I have the baby,
and I have Ross
and I just, I don't
know what to do
and I have to be at the office
and see Gavin in ten minutes.
Wow.
Sounds like you need to think
about what you want
and talk to Gavin, and you
definitely should talk to Ross.
Or...
I could call in sick
and not deal with it at all.
Wow.
Five month's maternity leave,
you're back for four days
kiss a coworker
and call in sick.
They are lucky
to have you.
Hi.
I, uh, I'm here
for my eyebrow
appointment.
Name?
Chandler Bing.
Okay, very good.
Have a seat right
over here, Mr. Bing,
and Sonya will be
right with you.
Okay, thanks.
Mm-hmm.
Ooh.
Ooh, ooh, ooh.
Ooh. Ooh.
Uh-oh.
I, uh, I touched the stuff.
I'll take
care of it.
Thanks.
So do you, uh...
do you get a lot
of guys in here?
Oh, absolutely.
Oh, good.
Yeah. You looking
to meet somebody?
All right, let's
just do this, okay?
Okay, uh, we'll get
to the wax in minute.
First, I want to tweeze
some of the strays, okay?
Now, this may sting
just a little bit...
Please, I have an extremely
high threshold for...
Holy Mother of God!
Oh! My face!
My face! Oh!
Hah.
I'm all right.
Just a, uh, bit
of a shock is all...
but, uh, I'll be fine.
You can go again,
I'm okay.
Okay.
Sorry.
Damn it, woman!
Ow!
Ow, ow!
Oh!
Oh, ow...
Okay, okay.
Hey.
Hey, it's the most eligible man
in New York.
How's the moving on going?
Not well.
I went on the subway again,
and someone did sit on my hand,
but that person was neither
female nor wearing pants.
Well, maybe you're going
about this the wrong way.
You know, I mean
think about it.
Single white male,
divorced three times,
two illegitimate children.
The personal ad writes itself.
You know, that's funny.
Yeah, do you, so do you think
you'll ever work again?
What are you doing?
You know I can only
dish it out.
I can't believe Rachel
just moved on
and-and didn't
say anything to me.
Look, maybe she didn't
move on, you know?
I mean, maybe that kiss
was just an impulsive
one-time birthday thing.
No. About a month ago
she gave her number
to some guy in a bar.
Did she go out with him?
No. When he called,
I threw the message away.
Ah, the high road.
All right, you know what?
Enough, enough talking.
I, I have to get moving.
Hey, check out those
two blondes over there.
Hey, come with me.
Are you trying to get
everybody divorced?
Come on. You don't
have to do anything.
It'll just be easier
if it's the two of us.
Like college, remember?
First, you, uh, break the ice
with some kind of a joke
so they know you're the funny
one, then I swoop in
with some interesting
conversation
so they'll see that I'm the
brilliant, brooding sexy one.
I thought I got to
make the jokes.
Don't you have to be at work?
Oh, come on!
Ah, hello.
Hi.
Uh, my name's Chandler.
This is my friend Ross
right here.
Hi.
And, uh, we were wondering,
you know,
if you're up for it.
We only need six more people
for a human pyramid.
Swoop, swoop!
Uh, so, um...
Oh, hey, I notice
you're reading the paper.
Uh, another flood
in Europe, huh?
Um, here's a question.
Would you, would you rather
drown or be burned alive?
Uh, sorry.
We're just leaving.
Okay.
We still got it.
( knock at door )
Who is it?
Gavin.
I brought you
some soup.
Why?
Uh, uh, I heard
you were sick.
Oh, right.
Yeah. Hold on,
let me just clean up
in here a little bit.
( weakly ):
Hello, Gavin.
I missed you at work today.
How you feeling?
I'm not going
to lie to you.
I'm pretty sick.
Oh, good, because I was having
a totally paranoid moment
where I thought
you called in sick to avoid me.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
( coughs )
No.
So... I had fun last night.
So did I.
Exactly how contagious
is this thing you have?
I mean, is it a cold
from standing on the balcony
or did a monkey bite ya?
It's just a cold.
You have a fever?
Let me see.
Mm.
Mmm...
Um...
What? What is it?
What's the matter?
What's Ross doing
to you in that picture?
Oh, he's dusting me
with a fossil brush.
He thought
it would be funny.
Right.
Ross.
Yeah.
So what's the deal
with you guys?
I don't want to get
in the middle of anything.
Oh... you're not.
You're not.
You're not getting in
the middle of anything.
Don't worry about Ross.
Really, really...
Oh, hide!
That's Ross.
Hide.
Hide, hide.
Yeah, but you said
not to worry about...
I lied, and I'm not sick either.
Just stay behind the curtain!
Hi.
Oh, Molly.
You're not Ross.
No. I'm here to take Emma
to your mother's, remember?
Right.
Yes, yes.
Don't panic.
What?
There's a man behind
your curtain.
I have mace in my purse...
No, that's okay,
that's okay...
No, no, no, no, no, no.
This is my business
associate Gavin.
He's just being silly.
Gavin, come out from behind
the curtain, you silly...
Hi.
Gavin.
Pleased to meet you.
It was my idea
to stand there.
Well, hello.
I'll, uh, I'll just
go get Emma.
Okay.
( clears throat )
So, um...
why did I have to hide?
I thought it was Ross.
So what if it was?
I thought there was nothing
going on between you two.
There isn't.
There totally isn't.
You hear keys in the hall and
you jump like a young bronco
coming out of the chute
for the first time.
I used to be
a rodeo clown.
Wow.
Uh, all right, look.
Gavin...
I...
I guess I-I felt guilty
that you were here.
Which I shouldn't.
You know, Ross and I are
not in a relationship.
But...
he is the father of my child.
And you know, we-we
do live together
and plus there's just
so much history, you know?
It's just...
I, I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I-I'm just all
over the place.
It's okay.
Now, I know it's probably
not my place,
but can I give you
a piece of advice?
Yes.
I think you should talk
to Ross about all this.
People keep saying that.
Oh, I'm sorry, Gavin.
Don't be.
It's just bad timing.
Mm.
So seriously, rodeo clown?
One of the best, ma'am,
one of the best.
( piano playing
"We Are the Champions" )
♪ No time for ♪
♪ Losers, 'cause we
are the champions ♪
♪ Of the world! ♪
Oh, she's my
girlfriend.
That's not just
how we do it here.
Uh, all right, I'm going
to take a little break
and, uh, when we come back,
we've got Kenneth
singing "I Touch Myself."
I'm not here to judge.
( giggles )
Oh, you have got to sing.
No, I told you I can't.
But you would have so much fun!
And you have
a really nice voice.
When have you heard me sing?
All the time
when you're cooking.
What?
Yeah, you're always singing
"Yummy, yummy, yummy,
I've got love in my tummy."
Yeah, I do rock that one.
Okay, so isn't there
just a little part of you
that wants to get up there?
Oh, just a little.
But it's just,
God, it's so scary.
I mean, I don't even know
what I would sing.
Well, I've got a book around...
"Delta Dawn."
Hi. I, uh, I couldn't help
but notice, uh, but that's
that's an unusual necklace.
You already hit on me
an hour ago.
Right.
So that's a firm no.
I don't believe this.
I just keep striking out.
I don't get it either.
I mean, you're obviously
desperate.
You're asking women
how they want to be killed.
Oh, this is great.
Rachel's going
to keep kissing guys
until she find
the one she wants,
and I'm, I'm going to die alone.
By drowning, or...
Why would he break up with me?
Oh, I don't know, sweety.
All I ever wanted
was to just love him
and have him
love me back.
I mean, am I
so unlovable?
( sobs )
Wow.
I know!
( piano plays ending flourish)
MIKE:
All right.
That was Kenneth
with his much too literal
rendition of "I Touch Myself."
Coming up next, we've got Monica
singing "Delta Dawn."
Oh, wait, wait.
I can't sing in front
of all these people.
Well, just pretend
they're not even here.
It's okay.
Monica, once that
spotlight hits you,
it's so bright, you
won't see anyone anyway.
Oh...
Hi, I'm Monica
and I'm going to be singing
"Delta Dawn."
( applause )
Ooh!
♪ Delta Dawn, what's
that flower you have on? ♪
♪ Could it be a faded rose
from days gone by? ♪
Can you totally see
through her shirt?
Like an X ray.
( men cheering and applauding )
Bad day not to wear a bra.
♪ ...Take you
to that mansion in the sky ♪
♪ She's 41, and... ♪
Hey.
I need your help.
Wow, it seems serious.
What seems to be
the problem, Ashley Judd?
Okay, look-- I'm getting
new headshots taken, all right?
So I went to get
my eyebrows shaped....
I'm sorry.
Moment to make fun
of that, please.
Okay, I may be a sissy, but I'll
still pound you into the ground.
Okay, all right, look.
It hurt so bad,
I could only let her do
one eyebrow and now...
they don't match!
Huh?
It's like a baby caterpillar
chasing its mama.
All right,
all right, look.
You've got to help
me out, okay?
Look I have a
magic marker.
I want you to fill
in the skinny one
so I don't look stupid
for my pictures.
Okay, first of all,
this is green.
Oh!
Well, what the hell
am I supposed to do?
All right, I will
help you out
but you have to promise me
you will not tell anyone
what I am about to tell you.
What?
Okay.
You know how most kids
get their allowance
from mowing the lawn or
taking out the garbage?
Well, I earned mine by
plucking the eyebrows
of my father and his...
"business partners."
( laughs )
Oh, my God.
Yeah, well, I guess you don't
need my help, Victor/Victoria.
Okay, all right,
no, no, no, I do.
I do. I do.
I need your help.
But, Chandler, I don't know
if I can take any more plucking.
It hurt so bad.
Oh, not with my combination
of ice cubes, aloe vera,
and my gentle...
self-loathing touch.
♪ To take you to that mansion
in the sky! ♪
( disappointed groans )
I'm sorry.
The song's over.
( disappointed groans )
Did you see me
up there?
Every little
bit of you.
Oh! I, I can't believe I did it!
I can't believe I sang in front
of people and they liked me.
Hey, did you hear that one guy
shouting "Look at those tips"?
I mean, did I really help you
get a lot of tips?
Sure.
Wow.
Okay, Mon.
Not that you didn't
sound good...
Good?
Didn't you hear them?
I was great!
Oh, thank you so much
for making me do this.
That is the best gift ever.
Also good gift--
underwear.
Thank you so much
for letting me do this.
Public bathrooms
freak me out.
I can't even pee,
let alone do anything else.
But what's great is you
don't mind talking about it.
God, it's so amazing
that I met you
on the same day that Eric
broke up with me,
'cause it's, like, you lose a
boyfriend, you get a boyfriend.
Uh-huh.
Look, no, no, no.
Don't worry.
This is not some
rebound thing.
I am totally over Eric.
Phew!
Okay.
Good choice, Ross.
Oh, hey!
Hi.
There you are.
I've been looking for you
everywhere.
Oh, yeah, hello.
Well, here, here I am.
Hey, listen, my mom
is not bringing the baby
back until 9:00.
So I was hoping you and I could
have a chance to kind of talk...
( toilet flushes )
Somebody here?
Oh, yeah, yeah,
that's Michelle.
Who?
Oh, just this woman
I've been seeing.
You've been seeing someone?
Yeah.
Didn't I mention that?
Yeah, uh, yeah.
Uh, uh...
I mean, we haven't been
going out too long, but, uh,
there's this amazing
connection between us.
Um, I-I-I mean, even
just before you came in
she called me her boyfriend.
I thought it was
a little too soon,
but also, you know,
it felt kind of nice.
What are you taking
amoxicillin for?
How great is this?
You, you're already
comfortable enough
to look through my stuff.
Uh, I'm sorry.
Michelle, this is
my roommate, Rachel.
Hi, and I'm also Emma's mother.
Oh, who's Emma?
Oh, I-I told you
about my daughter.
This is your daughter?
Yeah, I could be
your new mommy.
And done.
Oh, my God!
I didn't feel a thing.
Hey, are you still
looking for a job?
'Cause you could
tweeze circles
around that sadistic
bitch at the salon.
Thanks.
You want to see
what it looks like?
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, they totally match.
They look great.
How you doing?
Yeah, yeah, I think
it looks pretty good.
I was a little bit worried
that I was, uh, uncovering a
birthmark right about there.
But it turned out to be a
little piece of chocolate.
Huh.
Hey, Chandler,
thank you so much.
No problem.
Listen, uh...
that was a pretty girly
hour we just spent.
We should probably do something
manly to make up for it.
Yeah.
Curl my eyelashes.
Yeah!
Okay, for my next song,
I think I'll sing something
a little more upbeat.
All right, um...
Oh, how about the Pointer
Sisters "I'm So Excited"?
And make it bouncy.
Well, you'll probably take
care of that on your end.
I'm sorry I'm late.
You'll understand
when you see Joey.
Honey,
honey, you're
just in time.
I'm about to
sing another song.
Really? In front
of all these people?
And they love me!
Oh, my God.
Yeah, she gives the people
what they want.
Okay!
All right, watch!
( hooting and applauding )
♪ Tonight, tonight,
we're gonna make it happen ♪
♪ Tonight, we'll put
all other things aside ♪
♪ Get in this time
and show me some affection ♪
Are those my
wife's nipples?
♪ We're going
for those pleasures... ♪
Oh, isn't that funny?
I didn't see that before.
I wouldn't have let
her go up again.
Well, I've got
to stop this.
♪ To love you... ♪
( booing )
( cheering )
Ah, who cares?
They still love me.
( cheers and applause )
♪ I'm so excited... ♪
You!
Touching yourself!
Out!
( toilet flushes )
Wow.
She does that a lot.
Ross, you didn't tell me
you were a doctor!
Whoa-whoa, wait a minute.
You haven't even told her
that you were a doctor yet?
How long have you know her?
Like an hour?
Actually, about an
hour and a half.
I, I told you
it wasn't long, but, uh...
there's an amazing
connection between us.
You feel that, too?
Oh!
I thought that
that was just me!
Well, are-are
you kidding?
Um, hey, do you want
to go away this weekend?
We'll see.
Okay, Ross, what's
going on here?
Are we just bringing strange
women back to the apartment now?
I don't know.
Are we just kissing
guys on balconies?
What?
How do you know about that?
Through the magic of sight!
I was here putting
our child to sleep...
Emma.
When I happened to look
through the window
and see you kissing a guy
you've known for what?
A week?
Oh, God, is that what
this is all about?
Did you bring her up
here to get back at me?
No, actually,
see, I had to pee,
'cause I can't use
public bathrooms
because
of the doody parasites...
Okay, Michelle, it's time to go.
Well, call me.
Okay.
No wait! You don't
have my phone number.
Um, you know what?
If it's meant to be,
I'll guess it.
Bye-bye.
Score.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did you not like her?
Because I was hoping
maybe we could come
to one of your kissing
parties on the balcony.
Oh, God, you know,
I can't believe
you're making
such a big deal about this.
It was one kiss,
one guy, one time.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
What about the guy
from the bar?
What, who?
The guy you gave
your number to.
How do you know
about that?
Because he called
here looking for you.
So don't tell me this-this
kissing this guy from work
is a one-time thing, okay?
'Cause you been out there
in-in bars and on balconies
for over a month now,
and you didn't even have
the courtesy to tell me.
Why didn't I get
that message?
What?
From the guy
in the bar.
Why didn't I get
that message?
Because I folded it up
and put it in my pants pocket.
Do you, do you not look there?
Ross.
I never gave it to you.
Why?
I, I don't know.
Oh, God, you know what?
I don't...
Who do you think you are?
Who are you to decide
what messages I should
or should not get?
Who am I?
Yes!
I'm the guy who's
taking care of our baby
while you're out
at bars meeting guys.
Oh, my God, I cannot
believe you.
You know, I actually
came in here hoping
to have a mature
conversation with you
about us, but I
can't do that
with someone who
hides my messages
and brings crazy women
back to my apartment.
Hey! None of the sane ones
wanted to come back with me.
That's not...
it's not the point!
Okay?
The point is you-you
are the one who moved on
and didn't tell anyone.
Oh, God, Ross,
this is just so messed up!
What is wrong with us?
You know,
when people hear
about our situation,
they always ask,
"What, you live together,
but you're not a couple?
And yet you have a baby?
Isn't that weird?"
Ands I say "You know,
you know what?
It's not, because it
works for us."
But you know what?
This doesn't work.
In fact, this is
the-the opposite of working.
Ah, clearly.
And you know...
we said that we would,
we would live together
as long as this makes sense.
And maybe this, you know, just
doesn't make sense anymore.
Yeah, maybe not.
So what do you
want to do?
( knocking at door )
Hey.
Hi.
Can Emma and I live
here for a while?
God, uh...
Of course.
Thank you.
Oh.
Your eyebrows look weird.
♪ Jeremiah was a bullfrog ♪
♪ Was a good friend of mine ♪
♪ Never understood
a single word he said ♪
♪ but I helped him
drink his wine... ♪
So you'll just touch
yourself for anything, then.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org